Duc Minh Nguyen

Kokkola, Central Ostrobothnia, Finland

nguyenminhkhmt@gmail.com

+358 466272855

linkedin.com/in/duc-minh-nguyen-7190466b

Summary

I am a 33-year-old man with 9 years of iOS development experience. I am not afraid when I lose time. I am just afraid when I do not have the will. Persistence is my primary point.

I have a strong skill set to adapt to your requirements for this position because I've worked with Swift for more than 5 years. Before that, I worked with Objective-C and Obj-C++. I also have skills with JS when working directly with a browser application. I can set up an enterprise application from scratch. I am also familiar with many kinds of third libraries or creating/maintaining iOS SDKs.

Experience



🎸 Senior Software Engineer

Cốc Cốc

Apr 2020 - Present (2 years 8 months +)

Main tasks:

- Maintain iOS browser application on mobile
- Design and develop new features
- CI/CD integration

Team size: 6

Skills: iOS, C/C++, CI/CD, Objective-C++, Chromium, Javascript, MVVM,

Clean Architecture, MVVM-C, MVC, Viper, Swift UI, BLE

Software Developer

Innovation Technologies JSC (InnoTech)

Nov 2015 - Jan 2020 (4 years 3 months)

Senior iOS developer at Innotech Co.Ltd, Mobile Team leader

Main tasks performed:

- Mobile team lead (6 members); take care of the quality of Mobile client production.
- Worked as an agile team, designed and developed main functions.
- Design and develop mobile applications, training newbies, maintenance applications on the App Store.
- CI/CD integration
- Maintain internal frameworks PKI/OTP/EKYC
- Design & Develop a new framework for the Fido feature
- CI/CD integration

Skills: iOS, DJI SDK, Stripe, BuddyBuild, Fastlane, Kotlin, git, CouchBase, video/image processing

Team size: 8

Skills & Tech: iOS, C/C++, Cl/CD, PM, svn, git, Realm, Viper, Android, Lua script, Jenkins, Shadow,

Appium, Acronis, OpenCV, TesseractOCR, Vision, Crypto.

iOS developer

Savvycom - Software Product Development

Aug 2012 - Oct 2015 (3 years 3 months)

Senior iOS developer at Savvycom Software Co.Ltd

Main tasks performed:

Designed, wrote, and maintained high-quality software.

Developed, fixed bugs new products, and added new functionality to existing applications.

Team size: 20

Skills: iOS, git, Firebase, AFNetworking, CoreData

Education



Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Computer Science 2007 - 2012

Skills

Swift • Objective-C • OOP • JavaScript • C++ • Model-view-viewmodel (MVVM) • Viper • Agile Methodologies • Test Driven Development • iOS Development